A Guide to the Records of the Virginia 350th Anniversary Commission, 1953-1958 (bulk 1954-1957)
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Virginia 350th Anniversary Commission, 1953-1958
The Library of Virginia
25869
12 cu. ft. (33 boxes, 1 map case drawer)
Virginia 350th Anniversary Commission
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred by Mrs. J. M. Larson, Records Officer, Jamestown Foundation, Williamsburg, Virginia, 09/24/1963.
Biographical Information
The 350th Anniversary Commission was created by an act of the General Assembly passed on April 3, 1954 to develop and coordinate the plans of public and private agencies to commemorate the landing of the first colonists at Jamestown. Seventeen members were appointed to the commission for terms to expire December 31, 1957. In conformity with the act, an executive director, Mr. Parke Rouse, was named and a non-profit corporation, the Virginia 350th Anniversary Celebration Corporation, was created. The U.S. Congress also created the U.S. Jamestown-Williamsburg-Yorktown Celebration Commission to work in conjunction with the state commission.
The commission organized a celebration of nationwide interest and lasting value. The 1957 observance was known as "The Jamestown Festival" and the promotion was directed at the entire nation. The work of the commission divided itself into five major functions. The first was the development of a continuing central program for the eight month festival including exhibits, living history, religious functions, commemorative items, and cultural and entertainment events. The second function was to develop special commemorative events for specific celebrations. Thirdly, the commission sought to conduct research, direct archaeological exploration, perform microfilming of archival material and produce scholarly publications in order to define more clearly the importance of Jamestown and the contribution of Virginia settlers. One of the major accomplishments in this area was the creation of the Virginia Colonial Records Project to microfilm the colonial records of Virginia in housed British repositories. The fourth of the major efforts was to provide buildings and grounds essential to the central program, which resulted in the construction of Jamestown Festival Park, complete with information center, exhibit hall, and full-scale reconstructions of the three ships that brought the first colonists. The last major function of the commission was to coordinate the efforts of government agencies, localities, educational institutions, other historic sites, and cultural, professional and trade organizations.
In March 1958 the General Assembly passed an act to create the Jamestown Foundation to administer the development and operation of Jamestown Festival Park. The name of the foundation was changed to the Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation on July 1, 1976.
Scope and Content
Contains correspondence, brochures, programs, reports, press releases, architectural drawings, maps and newspaper articles that document the planning, fundraising and construction that occurred prior to the 350th anniversary celebration in 1957 of the first landing at Jamestown, Virginia.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. General files, 1953-1958
Arrangement is alphabetical by subject.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Separated Material
Oversize items can be found in box 33, map case 24, drawer 1, and map case OS-3, drawer 12. (See separation notices in folders).
Contents List
- Series I. General files, 1953-1958., Extent: 33 boxes. (Box 1-33)
  Contains correspondence and other papers from the office of the executive director of the Virginia 350th Anniversary Commission that provide insight into the events of The Jamestown Festival as they took place at Jamestown Festival Park, and around the state of Virginia during 1957. Most of the correspondence originated from the office of Mr. Parke Rouse, executive director of the Commission.
  Notable correspondents include important Virginia figures such as Senator Lloyd C. Bird and Governor Thomas B. Stanley, as well as Virginia native and philanthropist Mrs. Jessie Ball duPont, (wife of Mr. Alfred I. duPont). The visit of Queen Elizabeth II to the festival is well-documented, as is the commemorative tour of Europe taken by members of the Commission and other prominent Virginians. Files pertaining to the many special events and days of celebration in 1957 make up a large portion of the collection. Also included is information on committee functions, budgetary matters, fundraising, and participation by outside organizations. Additionally, there are architectural drawings and sketches which provide limited documentation of the park's structures and exhibits. Information on various excavation activities at the Green Spring, Glasshouse Point, and State House sites is also available.
  Within each folder the correspondence is arranged chronologically at the front. All other material is placed behind the correspondence, or is located in the final folder if there are multiple folders pertaining to one topic. The folders containing non-correspondence are always located at the rear, but may have date ranges that are the same or overlap the dates written on the correspondence folders.
  - Academy of Science Plans, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Act Creating Commission, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Addresses, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Admissions: Free Passes, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Advertising 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Agendas, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Agreements: Non-Profit and Corporation, 1955-1957 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - American Dairy Association Program, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - American Oil Company, 1955-1957 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - American Tobacco Company, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Annual Report, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Applications, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Arms and Armor, 1954-1956 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Arms and Armor, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Association for the Preservation of Virginia Antiquities, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Attorney General, Opinions of, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Automobile Tags, 1954-1956 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Baldridge, Tom, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Bids: Construction, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Bids: Food, 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Bids: Food, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Bids: Food, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bird, Lloyd C. (Senator), 1953-1956 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Boat Landing Policy, no date (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Book Sales, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - British Government, 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - British Government, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - British Government, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - British Scholars, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Budget, 1955-1958 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Budget: Fiscal Reports, 1955-1958 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Bus and Shuttle Proposals, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Celebrations, (similar), 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Certificates of Appreciation: No Cards, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Certificates of Appreciation: No Cards, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Certificates of Appreciation: No Cards, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Certificates of Appreciation: No Cards, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Certificates of Appreciation (sent): No Cards, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Certificates of Appreciation (sent): No Cards, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Charter, no date (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Charts, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - College of William and Mary, 1954-1956 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Colonial National Historical Park, 1954-1956 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Colonial National Historical Park, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Colonial National Historical Park, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Colonial Williamsburg, Inc., 1954-1956 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Color Production, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Color Production, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Commemorative Cruise, 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Commemorative Cruise, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Commemorative Cruise, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Commemorative Visit, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Commemorative Visit, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Commemorative Visit, 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Commemorative Visit, 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Commemorative Visit: Correspondence: William L. Shultz, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Commemorative Visit: Itineraries, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Commemorative Visit: Matieral Taken by Mr. Rouse, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Commemorative Visit: Material Taken by Mr. Rouse, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Commemorative Visit: Material Taken by Mr. Rouse, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Committee: Adivsory, 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Committee: Advisory, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Committee: Agricultural, Commercial and Industrial Expositions, 1954-1956 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Committee: Archives and History, 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Committee: Archives and History, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Committee: Archives and History, 1954-1956 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Committee: Archives and History: Subcommittee on Publications, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Committee: Archives and History: Subcommittee on Publications, 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Committee: Art, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Committee: Art, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Committee: Art, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Committee: Art, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Committee: Educational, 1954-1957 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Committee: Executive, 1954-1956 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Committee: Finance, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Committee: Finance, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Committee: Finance, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Committee: Finance, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Committee: Finance, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Committee: Finance, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Committee: Finance, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Committee: Finance, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Committee: Finance: Contribution Information, 1955-1957 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Committee: Finance: Corporation, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Committee: Highway Beautification, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Committee: Highway Beautification, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Committee: Highway Beautification, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Committee: Religious Functions and Observances, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Committee: Religious Functions and Observances, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Committee: Religious Functions and Observances, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Committee: Religious Functions and Observances, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Committee: Religious Functions and Observances, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - The Common Glory, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Commonwealth Youth Movement, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Concessions, 1954-1956 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Concessions, 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Contracts: Jamestown, Williamsburg, Yorktown Celebration Commission, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Conventions, 1954-1956 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1956-1957 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Costumes, 1954-1956 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Docking of Ships, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Docking of Ships, 1956-1957 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Early American Music, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - English Speaking Union, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Entertainment, 1954-1956 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Exhibits: British, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Exhibits: Miscellaneous, 1954-1955 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Exhibits: Miscellaneous, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Exhibits: Miscellaneous, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Exhibits: Miscellaneous, 1954-1956 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Exhibits: New World, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Exhibits: New World, 1956-1957 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Exhibits: New World, 1956-1957 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Federal Commission, 1955-1957 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Festival Information Center, 1954-1955 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Festival Information Center, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Festival Information Stations, 1954-1956 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Festival Reservations Bureau: Office Equipment, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Federal Reservations Bureau: Personnel, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Federal Reservations Bureau: Publicity, 1956-1957 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Films: State Board of Education, 1954-1956 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Finance: Publications, 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - First Virginia Militia, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Flags, 1954-1955 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Flags, 1956-1957 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Flags: State, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Flags: State, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Fundraising: Planning, 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Fundraising: Reconstruction of Ships, 1955-1957 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Fundraising: Sources, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Fundraising: Sources, 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Fundraising: Sources, 1956-1957 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Fundraising: Sources, 1955-1957 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Fundraising Sources: Mrs. Jessie Ball duPont, (Mrs. Alfred I. duPont), 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Glasshouse Point, 1954-1955 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Glasshouse Point, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Glasshouse Point, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Glasshouse Point, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Glass Works, 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Governor's Conference, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Green Spring: Design, 1954-1955 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Green Spring: Design, 1954-1956 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Green Spring: Miscellaneous, 1954-1956 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Green Spring: Property, 1954-1955 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Green Spring: Research, 1954-1956 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Green Spring: Research, 1954-1956 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Green Spring Report Mailing List, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Health Facilities, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - High School Dramas, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Historical Booklets, 1955-1957 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - H.M.S. Bigbury Bay Visit, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - House Document 12, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - House Document 25, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Housing, 1954-1955 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Housing: Pullman City, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Housing: Ship City, 1954-1956 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Housing: State Survey, 1954-1955 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Insect Control, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Invitations, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - James Fort, 1955-1956 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - James Fort: Construction, 1955-1956 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - James Fort: Construction, 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - James Fort: Construction, 1955-1957 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Jamestown 4-H Camp, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Jamestown Historical Films and Filmstrips (list of), no date (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Jamestown Park, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Jamestown Park, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Jamestown Park, 1955-1956 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Keel-laying, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Kemp, Verbon E., 1954-1955 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Kingsmill, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - League of Virginia Counties, 1954-1955 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Legal Opinions, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Library, 1954-1955 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Lord Mayor of London Visit, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Lord Mayor of London Visit, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Maps (correspondence about), 1955-1956 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Meetings, 1954-1956 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Meetings: State, City and County Officials, 1954-1955 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Meetings: State, City and County Officials, 1955-1956 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Military Participation, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Mooring Basin, 1956-1957 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Motion Pictures, 1954-1955 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Motion Pictures, 1955-1956 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Music: Ode to the Virginian Voyage by Randall Thompson, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Musical and Dramatic Events, 1956-1957 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Musical and Dramatic Events, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Musical and Dramatic Events, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Naturalized Citizens of America, Inc., 1954-1955 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Naturalized Citizens of America, Inc., 1955-1956 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Naturalized Citizens of America, Inc., 1956 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Nelson, Robert F., 1954-1955 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Patriotic Societies: Children of the American Revolution, 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Patriotic Societies: Colonial Dames of the 17th Century, 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Patriotic Societies: Colonial Daughters of the 17th Century, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Patriotic Societies: Daughters of Founders and Patriots of America, 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Patriotic Societies: Daughters of the American Colonists, 1955-1957 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Patriotic Societies: Daughters of the American Revolution, Great Bridge Chapter, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Patriotic Societies: Daughters of the American Revolution, State Society, 1955-1957 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Patriotic Societies: Descendants of the Signers of the Declaration of Independence, 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Patriotic Societies: Huguenot Society of the Founders of Manakin in the Colony of Virginia, 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Patriotic Societies: Jamestown Society, 1955-1957 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Patriotic Societies: Order of the First Families of Virginia, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Patriotic Societies: Order of the Founders and Patriots of America, 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Patriotic Societies: Society of Colonial Wars and Colonial Dames, 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Patriotic Societies: Society of Mayflower Descendants, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Patriotic Societies: Sons of the American Revolution, 1956-1957 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Hall (photograph of architectural drawing), no date (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Photography Policy, no date (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Planning: Preliminary, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Plans and Proposals, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Plans: Armory, 1954-1955 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Plans: Colonial Williamsburg, no date (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Plans: Green Spring, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Plans: Jamestown Island, no date (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Plans: State House, 1954-1957 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Plans: Williamsburg City, no date (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Plans: Williamsburg Traffic Flow, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Press Releases, 1954-1956 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Printing, 1956-1957 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Priorities, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Progress Report, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Publications, 1954-1955 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Publications, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Publications, 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Publications, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Publications, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Publications, 1956-1957 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Publications Program, 1954-1955 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Public Address System, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Publicity: Contacts, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Publicity Contacts, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Publicity Contacts, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Publicity: Planning, 1955-1956 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Publicity: Promotion, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Publicity: Promotion, 1955-1956 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Publicity: Promotion, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Publicity: Promotion, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Publicity: Promotion, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Publicity: Promotion, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Publicity: Promotion, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Public Relations, 1955-1956 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Public Relations, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Public Relations, 1955-1956 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Public Relations Conference, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Queen Mother's Visit, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Queen's Visit: Dinner and Reception, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Queen's Visit: Dinner and Reception, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Queen's Visit: Dinner and Reception, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Queen's Visit: Expenses, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Queen's Visit: Gifts, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Queen's Visit: Guest Accommodations, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Queen's Visit: Letters of Thanks, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Queen's Visit: Miscellaneous, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Queen's Visit: Newspaper Clippings, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Queen's Visit: Press, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Queen's Visit: Schedule, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Queen's Visit: Schedule, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Queen's Visit: Schedule, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Queen's Visit: Service at Jamestown Island, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Reese, Dr. George H. (personal), 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Religion, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Research, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Resolutions, 1954-1956 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Roads: New, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Roads: Traffic, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Roads: Williamsburg Area, Proposed, 1954-1955 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - St. Luke's Restoration, 1954-1956 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Seal, 1954-1955 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Seal, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Seal, 1954-1956 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Services Offered, 1954-1955 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Services Offered, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Services Offered, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Services Offered, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Ships: Christening, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Ships: Construction, 1955-1956 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Ships: Construction, 1955-1956 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Ships: Design, 1953-1956 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Ships: Miscellaneous, 1955-1956 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Ships: Names, 1955-1956 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Southern Bank of Norfolk, 1955-1957 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Souvenir Program, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Souvenir Program, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Souvenirs, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Souvenirs, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Souvenirs, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Souvenirs, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Souvenirs, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Special Days, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Special Days, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Special Days: Cape Henry Landing Reenactment, 1955-1957 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Special Days: Cape Henry Landing Reenactment, 1955-1957 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Special Days: Cathedral Cross Dedication, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Special Days: Cherry Tree Presentation, 1956-1957 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Special Days: Civic Club Day, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Special Days: College of William and Mary, 1955-1957 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Special Days: De Grasse Day, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Special Days: First Communion Celebration, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Special Days: General Assembly Day, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Special Days: General Assembly Day, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Special Days: General Assembly Day, 1956-1957 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Special Days: Goronwy Owen Day, 1956-1957 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Special Days: Governors, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Special Days: Greek Orthodox Pilgrimage, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Special Days: Hampton Day Celebration, 1955-1957 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Special Days: Hanover County Day, 1956-1957 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Special Days: International Naval Review, 1954-1957 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Special Days: International Naval Review, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Special Days: International Naval Review, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Special Days: International Naval Review, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Special Days: Jamestown Day, 1955-1957 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Special Days: Jamestown Day, 1955-1957 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Special Days: Jamestown Day: Presidential Proclamation, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Special Days: Jesuit Dedication, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Special Days: Newport News Celebration, 1956-1957 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Special Days: Nova Scotia Day, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 7)